<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cody Zanga&#39;s Sports Blog</title>
    <link>http://codyzanga.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cody Zanga&#39;s Sports Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://codyzanga.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The best NBA teams and players</title>
      <link>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/11/28/nba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/11/28/nba/</guid>
      <description>The NBA season is just around quarter mark in the 2022 season and there are already some teams and players that are separating from the rest of the pack. As with other sports, there are different ways we can look to judge and evaluate each team. Even though it’s still early in the season, we can look to see how things are trending right now.
Using data from basketball-reference, we’re going to look at how thing stand currently in the NBA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who are the best teams in the NFL?</title>
      <link>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/11/17/nfl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/11/17/nfl/</guid>
      <description>Currently we’re in week 10 of the 2022 NFL season and the potential playoff picture is beginning to take form. There’s many different ways you can judge how good a team is. You can use the eye test, simply watching the game and deciding who you think looks the best. You can also look at the teams win and loss record and how tough each teams schedule has been up to this point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ending the Mariners playoff drought.</title>
      <link>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/10/28/mariners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/10/28/mariners/</guid>
      <description>For those who don’t follow sports or baseball closely, the Seattle Mariners held the longest playoff drought across all professional North American sports teams. Coming into 2022, the drought had reached 20 years having last made the playoffs during a historic 2001 season that saw the team win 116 games.
Using data gathered from Baseball Reference, we’re going to take a look at how the Mariners ended the drought in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad umpire calls in MLB.</title>
      <link>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/10/07/umpires/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/10/07/umpires/</guid>
      <description>Umpires making bad calls is nothing new to baseball. Nearly every game there’s balls called strikes and strikes called balls, but how much impact does this really have on the outcome of every game that’s played throughout a regular MLB season? Fans of baseball no doubt can bring up moments where they feel like an entire at-bat is changed due to a bad call or even the outcome of the game has been shifted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is winning games connected to passer rating?</title>
      <link>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/04/30/passer-rating-and-wins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/04/30/passer-rating-and-wins/</guid>
      <description>For a while now it seems that there has been a lot of debate on how important passer rating really is for an NFL quarterback. There are other complex statistics out there such as QBR, which was created by ESPN to be a more accurate method to assess QB performance. QBR measures nearly everything a QB does including their turnovers, penalties and their performance compared to the rest of their team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Were the 2021 Mariners lucky, good or both?</title>
      <link>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/03/24/mariners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codyzanga.github.io/2022/03/24/mariners/</guid>
      <description>Fans of the Seattle Mariners have had to face more consistent ineptitude than almost any other professional team in American sports. For a team that has been around since 1977 to only have four playoff appearances is unacceptable. Currently, the last playoff appearance for the Mariners was in 2001, which was 21-years-ago. With that said, the Mariners are the proud owners of the longest playoff drought in American sports, but last season there was a glimmer of hope.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
